Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-272
  - Andres Small, The Cuban Promise for Tomorrow Case Studies on the Perspectives and Aspirations of Cuba's Youth, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)
  - Sexual Harrassment in Chile: Origins, Existence, Perspectives, 1996 Mar (Box 1)
  - Course reading for L.A.S. 126 The Politics of Environmental Degradation in Latin America, 1994 Spring (Box 1)
  - Course readings for Latin American Studies 251, 1992 Winter (Box 1)
  - The Changing of the Guard: The United States in Haiti, 1915-1993, 1993 Sep (Box 1)
  - The Political Economy of Privatization in Brazil, 1996 Jun (Box 1)
  - The Militarization of Honduras in the 1980's, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Debating Feminisms: The Latin American and Caribbean Feminist Encuentros (1981-1996), 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Museos Para la Paz. Propuesta Para la Definicion de un Nuevo Concepto de Museo Historico en Guatemala, 2000 Jul (Box 1)
  - Bridging the Linguistic Divide: A Study on How a Self-Help Center Assists Spanish-Speaking Latinos Achieve Meaningful Access to the California Courts, 2009 Jun (Box 1)
  - Texaco in Ecuador's Oriente Region: Towards a Theory of Transborder Legal Disputes, 1998 Jun 9 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Detras de los Nosotros que Ustedes Ven, Detras Estamos Ustedes: Renegotiating Citizenship in Zapatista Communities, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Ecuador: Caught in the Stalemate of Crises, 2001 Jun (Box 1)
  - Master of Arts in Latin American Studies Stanford University Capstone Journal Class of 2012, 2012 Jun (Box 1)
  - Chappel H. Lawson, Building the Fourth Estate, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Hector Perla, Neoliberal Reforms in El Salvador, 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)
  - Andres Small, The Cuban Promise for Tomorrow Case Studies on the Perspectives and Aspirations of Cuba's Youth, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)
  - Sexual Harrassment in Chile: Origins, Existence, Perspectives, 1996 Mar (Box 1)
  - Course reading for L.A.S. 126 The Politics of Environmental Degradation in Latin America, 1994 Spring (Box 1)
  - Course readings for Latin American Studies 251, 1992 Winter (Box 1)
  - The Changing of the Guard: The United States in Haiti, 1915-1993, 1993 Sep (Box 1)
  - The Political Economy of Privatization in Brazil, 1996 Jun (Box 1)
  - The Militarization of Honduras in the 1980's, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Debating Feminisms: The Latin American and Caribbean Feminist Encuentros (1981-1996), 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Museos Para la Paz. Propuesta Para la Definicion de un Nuevo Concepto de Museo Historico en Guatemala, 2000 Jul (Box 1)
  - Bridging the Linguistic Divide: A Study on How a Self-Help Center Assists Spanish-Speaking Latinos Achieve Meaningful Access to the California Courts, 2009 Jun (Box 1)
  - Texaco in Ecuador's Oriente Region: Towards a Theory of Transborder Legal Disputes, 1998 Jun 9 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Detras de los Nosotros que Ustedes Ven, Detras Estamos Ustedes: Renegotiating Citizenship in Zapatista Communities, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Ecuador: Caught in the Stalemate of Crises, 2001 Jun (Box 1)
  - Master of Arts in Latin American Studies Stanford University Capstone Journal Class of 2012, 2012 Jun (Box 1)
  - Latin American Studies MA Capstone Journal, Class of 2017 (Box 2)
  - Latin American Studies Program Material, 2002-2008 (Box 2)
  - Bolivar House Commencement, 2002-2008 (Box 2)